<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio on Arberia Theme</title><link>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolio on Arberia Theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:28:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python Rock Paper Scissors Game</title><link>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/python-rock-paper-scissors-game/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:13:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/python-rock-paper-scissors-game/</guid><description>Game programming is a great way to learn how to program. You use many tools that you’ll see in the real world, plus you get to play a game to test your results! An ideal game to start your Python game programming journey is rock paper scissors.
In this course, you’ll learn how to:
Code your own rock paper scissors game Take in user input with input() Play several games in a row using a while loop Clean up your code with Enum objects and functions Define more complex rules with a dictionary</description></item><item><title>Using Data Classes in Python</title><link>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/data-classes-python/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/data-classes-python/</guid><description>One new and exciting feature that came out in Python 3.7 was the data class. A data class is a class typically containing mainly data, although there aren’t really any restrictions.
With data classes, you don’t have to write boilerplate code to get proper initialization, representation, and comparisons for your objects.
In this course, you’ll learn how to:
Define your own data classes Add default values to the fields in your data class Customize the ordering of data class objects Work with immutable data classes</description></item><item><title>Testing Your Code With pytest</title><link>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/testing-code-pytest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/testing-code-pytest/</guid><description>Testing your code brings a wide variety of benefits. It increases your confidence that the code behaves as you expect and ensures that changes to your code won’t cause regressions. Writing and maintaining tests is hard work, so you should leverage all the tools at your disposal to make it as painless as possible. pytest is one of the best tools you can use to boost your testing productivity.
In this video course, you’ll learn:</description></item><item><title>Building a Django User Management System</title><link>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/building-django-user-management-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:24:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hugoarberiatheme.netlify.app/portfolio/building-django-user-management-system/</guid><description>If you’re building your own Django applications, you might decide to extend them with user accounts. In this video course, you’ll learn how to work with Django user management and add it to your program.
By the end of this video course, you’ll be able to:
Create an application where users can register, log in, and reset and change passwords on their own Edit the default Django templates responsible for user management Send password reset emails to actual email addresses Authenticate using an external service You may find it useful to complete Get Started With Django: Build a Portfolio App before beginning this course.</description></item></channel></rss>